Contact

precyrn2@aol.com

www.linkedin.com/in/prescillang (LinkedIn) www.designmywebprescilla.com (Company)

www.prescillang.com (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Surgical First Assisting (RNFA)
Peripheral Vascular Perioperative
Nursing

Cardiothoracic Perioperative Nursing

Languages

English (Professional Working)
Filipino (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

ACLS Provider
Registered Nurse
RNFA Program Completion
CVRN-BC
PALS Provider

Honors-Awards

CGFNS Certificate

American Shaolin Kung Fu Certificate of Rank

Tiger-Rock Martial Arts International TaeKwonDo Certificate

Prescilla Ng

BSN CNOR CVRN-BC RNFA

Houston, Texas Area

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse First Assist (RNFA) with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital and healthcare industry. Skilled in multi-specialty perioperative nursing and with 14 years of adult cardiovascular and thoracic perioperative RN experience. Strongly performs interchanging roles as first scrub nurse, circulating nurse, and charge nurse. RNFA program graduate from the National Institute of First Assisting, Inc. Acquired RNFA training in adult heart and lung transplants at Texas Heart Institute and congenital heart surgery RNFA experience at Texas Children's Hospital. American Board of Cardiovascular Medicine - Board Certified CV RN. Well rounded professional with strong entrepreneurship professional experience enhanced by social media marketing skills and learned success strategies. Educated and experienced in advanced options trading, real estate, and stocks investing. Condominium Business owner and Options Trader.

Experience

Memorial Hermann Hospital Heart and Vascular Institute - Texas Medical Center
CVOR Perioperative RN IV
March 2019 - Present (1 year 3 months)
Texas Medical Center

Credentialed at CHI St. Luke's Health - Baylor St. Luke's Medical Center

Allied Health RNFA February 2018 - Present (2 years 4 months)

Houston, Texas Area

Wisemoney Corporation Investor | Entrepreneur | Founding Partner January 2008 - Present (12 years 5 months) Sugar Land, Texas Texas Children's Hospital Congenital Heart Surgery RN First Assist May 2017 - October 2018 (1 year 6 months)

Houston, Texas

Texas Heart Institute / CHI St. Luke's Health - Baylor St. Luke's Medical Center
CVOR Perioperative Nurse
August 2007 - May 2017 (9 years 10 months)
Houston, Texas

Perioperative RN specialty on Adult Cardiac Surgery and Transplants (Kidney/Liver/Heart/Lungs)

Memorial Hermann Health System / Heart and Vascular Institute Cardio-Vascular and Thoracic Perioperative RN November 2004 - October 2007 (3 years) Houston, Texas Area

NTICU / CVOR

Houston Methodist
Perioperative RN Staff
May 2001 - November 2004 (3 years 7 months)
Houston, Texas Area

Price Memorial Skilled Nursing RN Charge Nurse November 1999 - February 2001 (1 year 4 months) Greater St. Louis Area

The Medical City
Multi-specialty Perioperative RN Staff
June 1998 - November 1999 (1 year 6 months)
Ortigas Center, Pasig City, Philippines

Dexaplast International Co. Ltd.
Occupational Health Nurse
November 1995 - May 1998 (2 years 7 months)
Quezon City, Philippines

ADL Marketing
Senior Marketing Manager

June 1994 - November 1995 (1 year 6 months)

Pasig City, Philippines

Filinvest Company
Area Manager

March 1993 - June 1994 (1 year 4 months)

Pasig City, Philippines

Education

Walden University

MSN, Adult-Gerontology Acute Care Nurse Practitioner · (2020 - 2023)

National Institute of First Asssisting, Inc.

RNFA Program · (2014 - 2016)

HCC Coleman College for Health Sciences

· (2012)

OX- Proprietary Entity

Advanced ETF, Forex, Futures and Options Trading (2006)

WIA - Proprietary Entity

Master Stock Trading and Advanced Options Trading (2004)